questions = [
        {
            "question": "what colour does red and blue make?",
            "options": ["green", "purple", "yellow", "orange"],
            "answer": 1,
            "category": "colour"
        },
        {
            "question": "what colour does yellow and green make?",
            "options": ["lime", "tangerine", "violet", "orange"],
            "answer": 0,
            "category": "colour"
        },
        {
            "question": "what colour does yellow and red make?",
            "options": ["brown", "purple", "pink", "orange"],
            "answer": 3,
            "category": "colour"
        },
        {
            "question": "what colour does white and red make?",
            "options": ["pink", "purple", "orange", "yellow"],
            "answer": 0,
            "category": "colour"
        },
        {
            "question": "what colour does blue and yellow make?",
            "options": ["purple", "orange", "green", "cyan"],
            "answer": 2,
            "category": "colour"
        },
        {
            "question": "what colour does purple and yellow make?",
            "options": ["purple", "orange", "green", "cyan"],
            "answer": 2,
            "category": "colour"
        },
        {
            "question": "what colour does pink and purple make?",
            "options": ["magenta", "blush pink", "cherry", "crimson"],
            "answer": 0,
            "category": "colour"
        },
        {
            "question": "what colour does blue and pink make?",
            "options": ["red", "purple", "orange", "brown"],
            "answer": 1,
            "category": "colour"
        },
        {
            "question": "what colour does orange and blue make?",
            "options": ["red", "pink", "yellow", "brown"],
            "answer": 3,
            "category": "colour"
        },
        {
            "question": "what colour does red and green make?",
            "options": ["red", "yellow", "orange", "brown"],
            "answer": 1,
            "category": "colour"
        },
        ]
    
    
